<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yinbo Yu | 于银菠 on Yinbo Yu</title>
    <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yinbo Yu | 于银菠 on Yinbo Yu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.yinbo.ml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Deployment Triggers</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/contributions/deploy-triggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/contributions/deploy-triggers/</guid>
      <description>Addressed pretty significant page load performance issue founde in larger deployments. Eliminates uses of intensive backend query, replacing it with an asynchronous API call against a lucene index. This change reduces page load from from 2+ minutes to nearly instant, with an incredibly responsive UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joint Optimization of Service Request Routing and Instance Placement in the Microservice System</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/lego/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/lego/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falcon: Differential Fault Location for SDN Control Plane</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/falcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/falcon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CellScope: Automatically Specifying and Verifying Cellular Network Protocols</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/cellscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/cellscope/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking inside the Box: Differential Fault Location for SDN Control Plane</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/thinking/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fault Management in Software-Defined Networking: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/sdnsurvey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/sdnsurvey/</guid>
      <description>This talk looked at Liberty Mutual’s transformation to Continuous Integration, Continuous Delivery, and DevOps. For a large, heavily regulated industry, this task can not only be daunting, but viewed by many as impossible. Often, organizations try to reduce the friction through micro-fixes, but Eddie’s team asked how to change the culture to reduce the friction and concluded with the following final points:
 Don’t mandate DevOps. Give employees the chance to master their discipline with examples to set and follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Added Docker Build Status Badge to shields.io</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/contributions/shields-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/contributions/shields-docker/</guid>
      <description>Shields.io is a massive library of badges that can be inserted into project README&amp;rsquo;s or websites displaying various statuses (code coverage, health, version, etc). Support for docker was missing the current build health, and was a pretty trivial addition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schema.org Structured Data documentation fixes</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/contributions/schema-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/contributions/schema-org/</guid>
      <description>While adding Structured Data to a client&amp;rsquo;s website I found some example JSON that was invalid. Simple contribution to cleanup the user documentation providing syntactically valid JSON documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatically specifying and verify cellular network protocols</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</guid>
      <description>CellScope is a specification and verification framework, CellScope, for exploiting design flawsin cellular network protocols. CellScope consists two major components: a parser frontend and a verification backend. The parser front-end automatically translates LTE source code to formal models and instruments channel and adversary models into LTE models. By slicing the model depending on a property, CellScope performs the CEGAR-based verification backend on it. Once a counterexample is identified, it will be validated on a real OAI testbed platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fault Location in the control plane of Software-defined Networking</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/falcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/falcon/</guid>
      <description>CellScope is a specification and verification framework, CellScope, for exploiting design flawsin cellular network protocols. CellScope consists two major components: a parser frontend and a verification backend. The parser front-end automatically translates LTE source code to formal models and instruments channel and adversary models into LTE models. By slicing the model depending on a property, CellScope performs the CEGAR-based verification backend on it. Once a counterexample is identified, it will be validated on a real OAI testbed platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Discovering and Repairing Security issues in configurable implementations of Cellular networks</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Multiple plugins used by thousands of teams that provide enhanced functionality of Atlassian’s core products (primarily JIRA and Bamboo) to enrich CI/CD capabilities, DevOps automation, or productivity. Functionality spans user interface, web services and persistence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;quot;HTML&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;JSON&amp;quot;]  Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service Request Routing and Instance Deployment in the Microservice-base cloud</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>