<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cellular network on Yinbo Yu</title>
    <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/tags/cellular-network/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cellular network on Yinbo Yu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.yinbo.ml/tags/cellular-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CellScope: Automatically Specifying and Verifying Cellular Network Protocols</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/cellscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/publications/cellscope/</guid>
      <description>This talk looked at Liberty Mutual’s transformation to Continuous Integration, Continuous Delivery, and DevOps. For a large, heavily regulated industry, this task can not only be daunting, but viewed by many as impossible. Often, organizations try to reduce the friction through micro-fixes, but Eddie’s team asked how to change the culture to reduce the friction and concluded with the following final points:
 Don’t mandate DevOps. Give employees the chance to master their discipline with examples to set and follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatically specifying and verify cellular network protocols</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</guid>
      <description>CellScope is a specification and verification framework, CellScope, for exploiting design flawsin cellular network protocols. CellScope consists two major components: a parser frontend and a verification backend. The parser front-end automatically translates LTE source code to formal models and instruments channel and adversary models into LTE models. By slicing the model depending on a property, CellScope performs the CEGAR-based verification backend on it. Once a counterexample is identified, it will be validated on a real OAI testbed platform.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>