<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creations on Yinbo Yu</title>
    <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creations on Yinbo Yu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatically specifying and verify cellular network protocols</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</guid>
      <description>CellScope is a specification and verification framework, CellScope, for exploiting design flawsin cellular network protocols. CellScope consists two major components: a parser frontend and a verification backend. The parser front-end automatically translates LTE source code to formal models and instruments channel and adversary models into LTE models. By slicing the model depending on a property, CellScope performs the CEGAR-based verification backend on it. Once a counterexample is identified, it will be validated on a real OAI testbed platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Marketplace Plugins</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Multiple plugins used by thousands of teams that provide enhanced functionality of Atlassian’s core products (primarily JIRA and Bamboo) to enrich CI/CD capabilities, DevOps automation, or productivity. Functionality spans user interface, web services and persistence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker image for Bitbucket CI/CD Pipelines  &#34;shipit&#34;</title>
      <link>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinbo.ml/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Provides required dependencies and additional utilities to simplify and codify the process of building, testing and delivering Atlassian plugins all the way to the live marketplace. Executes integration/AUT level tests against all stated compatible versions for the productUploads generated artifact to Atlassian marketplaceProvides corresponding metadata indicating version, release notes, and compatibility</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>